happy-mothering.com 2019-05-07

# Privacy Policy - Happy Mothering

_**Effective as of May 25, 2018**_

As the owner of this website (the “Site”), [name of Site owner] (“we” or “us”) understand that your privacy is of critical importance. This Privacy Policy describes what information we collect from you via the Site and how we use and disclose such information.

###  **Our Use of Cookies**

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry [date](https://amzn.to/2l7bAdC), unless deleted by the user before the expiry [date](https://amzn.to/2l7bAdC); a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed. Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

We use cookies for the following purposes:

(a) authentication – we use cookies to identify you when you visit our website and as you navigate our website;

(b) status – we use cookies to help us to determine if you are logged into our website;

(c) personalization – we use cookies to store information about your preferences and to personalize the website for you;

(d) security – we use cookies as an element of the security measures used to protect user accounts, including preventing fraudulent use of login credentials, and to protect our website and services generally;

(e) advertising – we use cookies to help us to display advertisements that will be relevant to you; and

(f) analysis – we use cookies [to help us to analyze the use and performance of our website and services;

We use Google Analytics to analyze the use of our website. Google Analytics gathers information about website use by means of cookies. The information gathered relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of our website. Google’s privacy policy is available at: <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies and to delete cookies. The methods for doing so vary from browser to browser, and from version to version. You can however obtain up-to-[date](https://amzn.to/2l7bAdC) information about blocking and deleting cookies via these links:

(a) <https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en> (Chrome);

(b) <https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences>(Firefox);

(c) [http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/](https://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/) (Opera);

(d) <https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies> (Internet Explorer);

(e) [https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411](https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411?locale=en_US) (Safari); and

(f) <https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy> (Edge).

Please note that blocking cookies may have a negative impact on the functions of many websites, including our Site. Some features of the Site may cease to be available to you.

##  **Interest-Based Advertising**

###  **Advertising Privacy Statement**

This Site is affiliated with AdThrive, LLC (“AdThrive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site. AdThrive uses standard and widely-available tools for the placement and serving of ads, including those provided by Google, Inc. and its affiliates. We publish interest-based advertisements on the Site; that is, ads that are tailored to reflect your interests. To help understand your interests, AdThrive, Google and our other advertising partners will track your behavior on our website and on other websites across the Internet using cookies.

By using this Site, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third party partners. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: [https://adssettings.google.com](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/html/blocked-cookies.html). You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative’s multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: [http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1). However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained.

###  **For European Economic Area Residents**

If you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing. If you wish to access or delete your personal data (if any) maintained by us or AdThrive related to advertising on the Site, you can contact AdThrive at info@adthrive.com. If you wish to see a list of the advertising partners we work with or change which of those partners track your behavior using cookies, click the ad preferences icon. (Available in the EU.)

###  **Email Addresses**

We may collect your email address, but only if you voluntarily provide it to us. This may occur, for example, if you sign up to receive an email newsletter, or enter a promotion. We will use your email address for the purposes for which you provided it to us, and also from time to time to send you emails regarding the Site or other products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. You may opt out of such email communications at any time by clicking the “unsubscribe” button in the email.

Your email address may also be shared with the technology provider we use in connection with the purposes for which you provided it, and that technology provider may also contact you from time to time.

If you are a resident of a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), please refer to the section below entitled “Additional Rights of EEA Residents.”

###  **Registration or Account Data**

We may collect other information from you when you register with our Site in order to use various features. Such information could include your name, birthday, postal code, screen name, and password (if applicable). As you use the Site, we could collect other data that you provide voluntarily (such as comments that you post).

We may also collect information about you through other methods, including research surveys, social media platforms, verification services, data services, as well as public sources. We may combine this data with your registration data in order to maintain a more thorough profile.

We may use third parties to provide the functionality to allow you to register for the Site, in which case the third party will also have access to your information. Otherwise, we will not provide any personally-identifying information about you to third parties, except if required by law.

We may use your personally-identifying information for a variety of our internal business purposes, such as creating a better user experience for the Site, diagnosing and troubleshooting malfunctions on the Site, better understanding how the Site is used, and making personalized recommendations to you.

If you are a resident of a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), please refer to the section below entitled “Additional Rights of EEA Residents.”

###  **Transactional Data**

We may process information relating to transactions, including purchases of goods and services, that you enter into with us and/or through our Site (“Transactional Data”). The Transactional Data may include your contact details, your card details and the transaction details. The transaction data may be processed for the purpose of supplying the purchased goods and services and keeping proper records of those transactions. [Payment processing on our Site is handled by our payment services providers, [identify PSPs]. We will share transaction data with our payment services providers only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing your payments, refunding such payments and dealing with complaints and queries relating to such payments and refunds. You can find information about the payment services providers’ privacy policies and practices at [URLs]]

###  **Additional Rights of EEA (European Economic Area) Residents**

If you are a resident of a country in the EEA, you have the rights, among others, to:

(i)  access your personal data

(ii)  ensure the accuracy of your personal data

(iii) the right to have us delete your personal data

(iv)  the right to restrict further processing of your personal data, and

(v)  the right to complain to a supervisory authority in your country of residence in the event that data is misused

If you believe that our processing of your personal information infringes data protection laws, you have a legal right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority responsible for data protection. You may do so in the EU member state of your residence, your place of work or the place of the alleged infringement.

You may exercise any of your rights in relation to your personal data by written notice to us addressed to the following:

Chrystal Johnson  
PO Box 708  
Big Bear Lake, CA 92315  
909-520-8694

###  **Sale of Business or Assets**

In the event that the Site or substantially all of its assets is sold or disposed of as a going concern, whether by merger, sale of assets or otherwise, or in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership, the information we have collected about you may be one of the assets sold or merged in connection with that transaction.

###  **Changes to the Privacy Policy**

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most recent version of the Privacy Policy will always be posted on the Site, with the “Effective Date” posted at the top of the Policy. We may revise and update this Privacy Policy if our practices change, as technology changes, or as we add new services or change existing ones. If we make any material changes to our Privacy Policy or how we handle your personal information, or we are going to use any personal information in a manner that is materially different from that stated in our Privacy Policy at the time we collected such information, we will give you a reasonable opportunity to consent to the change. If you do not consent, your personal information will be used as agreed to under the terms of the privacy policy in effect at the time we obtained that information. By using our Site or services after the Effective Date, you are deemed to consent to our then-current privacy policy. We will use information previously obtained in accordance with the Privacy Policy in effect when the information was obtained from you.

###  **Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or the practices of this Site, please contact us at chrystal@happymothering.com.

Or write to us at:

Chrystal Johnson  
PO Box 708  
Big Bear Lake, CA 92315

###  **Your Acceptance of These Terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
